Office of the Registrar fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Publications, 1965 - 2008; F-85-5; 4.13 m of textual records 732.52 GB of textual records (tiff, pdf): digitized copies 2 moving images
  - Academic calendars, 2016; 1965-2010; F-85-5-6; 1.75 m of textual records: originals 732.52 GB of textual records (tiff, pdf): digitized copies
    Paper and digital copies are available. The Archives digitized the entire series in 2015. For each calendar, there is a digital preservation master copy, comprised of one TIFF file for each page. The TIFF files were then compiled into a single OCR'ed PDF file as the access copy. The PDF copies are available directly from SFU AtoM. Contact the Reference Archivist for copies of the TIFF preservation master. The print editions can be accessed in the Archives' reading room.
    All items are open with no access restrictions.
    - 1965-66 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-1; F-85-5-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 85-26)
      - Simon Fraser University Calendar Volume 1, 1965-66, F-85-5-6-0-1-1
    - 1966-67 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-2; F-85-5-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 85-26)
      - Simon Fraser University Calendar Volume II, 1966-67, F-85-5-6-0-2-1
      - Simon Fraser University Graduate Studies Calendar 1966-67, F-85-5-6-0-2-2
    - 1967-68 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-3; F-85-5-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 85-26)
      - Simon Fraser University Calendar, 1967-68, F-85-5-6-0-3-1
      - Simon Fraser University Graduate Studies Calendar, 1967-68, F-85-5-6-0-3-2
    - 1968-69 Calendar, 1968-1969; F-85-5-6-0-4; F-85-5-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 85-26)
      - Simon Fraser University Calendar 1968-69, F-85-5-6-0-4-1
      - Simon Fraser University Graduate Studies Calendar 1968-69, F-85-5-6-0-4-2
      - Simon Fraser University 1969 Summer Addendum, F-85-5-6-0-4-3
    - 1969-70 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-5; F-85-5-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 85-26)
      - Simon Fraser University Calendar 1969-70, F-85-5-6-0-5-1
      - Simon Fraser University Graduate Studies Calendar 1969-70, F-85-5-6-0-5-2
    - 1970-71 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-6 (Archival box - standard 85-27)
      - 1970-71 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-6-1
      - 1970-71 Graduate Studies Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-6-2
    - 1971-72 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-7; F-85-5-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 85-27)
      - Simon Fraser University Calendar 1971-72, F-85-5-6-0-7-1
      - Simon Fraser University Graduate Studies Calendar 1971-72, F-85-5-6-0-7-2
    - 1972-73 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-8; F-85-5-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 85-27)
      - Simon Fraser University Calendar 1972-73, F-85-5-6-0-8-1
      - Simon Fraser University Graduate Studies Calendar 1972-73, F-85-5-6-0-8-2
    - 1973-74 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-9; F-85-5-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 85-27)
      - Simon Fraser University Calendar 1973-74, F-85-5-6-0-9-1
      - Simon Fraser University Graduate Studies Calendar 1973-74, F-85-5-6-0-9-2
    - 1974-75 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-10; F-85-5-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 85-27)
      - Simon Fraser University Calendar 1974-75, F-85-5-6-0-10-1
        Records in electronic form (digitized)
      - Simon Fraser University Graduate Studies Calendar 1974-75, F-85-5-6-0-10-2
    - 1975-76 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-11; F-85-5-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 85-28)
      - Simon Fraser University Calendar 1975-76, F-85-5-6-0-11-1
      - Simon Fraser University Graduate Studies Calendar 1975-76, F-85-5-6-0-11-2
    - 1976-77 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-12; F-85-5-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 85-28)
      - Simon Fraser University Calendar 1976-77, F-85-5-6-0-12-1
      - Simon Fraser University Graduate Studies Calendar 1976-77, F-85-5-6-0-12-2
    - 1977-78 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-13; F-85-5-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 85-28)
      - Simon Fraser University Calendar 1977-78, F-85-5-6-0-13-1
      - Simon Fraser University Graduate Studies Calendar 1977-78, F-85-5-6-0-13-2
        Records in electronic form (digitized); Textual records
    - 1978-79 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-14; F-85-5-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 85-28)
      - Simon Fraser University Calendar 1978-79, F-85-5-6-0-14-1
      - Simon Fraser University Graduate Studies Calendar 1978-79, F-85-5-6-0-14-2
    - 1979-80 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-15; F-85-5-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 85-29)
      - Simon Fraser University Calendar 1979-80, F-85-5-6-0-15-1
      - Simon Fraser University Graduate Studies Calendar 1979-80, F-85-5-6-0-15-2
    - 1980-81 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-16; F-85-5-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 85-29)
      - Simon Fraser University Undergraduate Studies Calendar 1980-81, F-85-5-6-0-16-1
      - Simon Fraser University Graduate Studies Calendar 1980-81, F-85-5-6-0-16-2
    - 1981-82 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-17; F-85-5-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 85-29)
      - Simon Fraser University Undergraduate Studies Calendar 1981-82, F-85-5-6-0-17-1
      - Simon Fraser University Graduate Studies Calendar 1981-82, F-85-5-6-0-17-2
    - 1982-83 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-18; F-85-5-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 85-30, Archival box - standard 85-31)
      - Simon Fraser University Calendar 1982/83, F-85-5-6-0-18-1
    - 1983-84 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-19; F-85-5-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 85-30, Archival box - standard 85-31)
      - 1983/84 Simon Fraser University Calendar: Undergraduate and Graduate Studies, F-85-5-6-0-19-1
    - 1984-85 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-20; F-85-5-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 85-30, Archival box - standard 85-31)
      - Simon Fraser University Calendar: 1984/85 Undergraduate and Graduate Studies, F-85-5-6-0-20-1
    - 1985-86 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-21; F-85-5-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 85-30, Archival box - standard 85-31)
      - Simon Fraser University Calendar 1985/1986
    - 1986-87 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-22; F-85-5-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 85-30, Archival box - standard 85-31)
      - Simon Fraser University Calendar 1986/87, F-85-5-6-0-22-1
    - 1987-88 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-23; F-85-5-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 85-30, Archival box - standard 85-31)
      - Simon Fraser University Calendar 1987-1988
    - 1988-89 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-24; F-85-5-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 85-30, Archival box - standard 85-31)
      - Simon Fraser University Calendar 1988/89, F-85-5-6-0-24-1
    - 1989-90 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-25; F-85-5-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 85-30, Archival box - standard 85-31)
      - Simon Fraser University Calendar 1989-1990, F-85-5-6-0-25-1
    - 1990-91 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-26; F-85-5-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 85-30, Archival box - standard 85-31)
      - Simon Fraser University Calendar 1990-1991
    - 1991-92 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-27; F-85-5-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 85-30, Archival box - standard 85-31)
      - Simon Fraser University Calendar, 1991-1992, F-85-5-6-0-27-1
    - 1992-93 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-28; F-85-5-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 85-32, Archival box - standard 85-33)
      - Simon Fraser University Calendar, 1992-1993, F-85-5-6-0-28-1
    - 1993-94 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-29; F-85-5-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 85-32, Archival box - standard 85-33)
      - Simon Fraser University 1993-1994 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-29-1
    - 1994-95 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-30; F-85-5-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 85-32, Archival box - standard 85-33)
      - Simon Fraser University Calendar, 1994-1995, F-85-5-6-0-30-1
    - 1995-96 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-31; F-85-5-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 85-32, Archival box - standard 85-33)
      - Simon Fraser University 1995/1996 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-31-1
    - 1996-97 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-32; F-85-5-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 85-32, Archival box - standard 85-33)
      - Simon Fraser University 1996-1997 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-32-1
    - 1997-98 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-33; F-85-5-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 85-32, Archival box - standard 85-33)
      - Simon Fraser University 1997-1998 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-33-1
    - 1998-99 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-34; F-85-5-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 85-32, Archival box - standard 85-33)
      - Simon Fraser University Calendar 1998-1999, F-85-5-6-0-34-1
    - 1999-00 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-35; F-85-5-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 85-32, Archival box - standard 85-33)
      - Simon Fraser University 1999/2000 Calendar
    - 2000-01 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-36; F-85-5-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 85-34)
      - Simon Fraser University Calendar 2000-2001, F-85-5-6-0-36-1
    - 2001-02 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-37; F-85-5-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 85-34)
      - Simon Fraser University Calendar 2001/2002, F-85-5-6-0-37-1
    - 2002-03 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-38; F-85-5-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 85-34)
      - Simon Fraser University 2002/2003 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-38-1
    - 2003-04 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-39; F-85-5-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 85-34)
      - Simon Fraser University Calendar 2003/2004, F-85-5-6-0-39-1
    - 2004-05 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-40; F-85-5-3-0-10 (Archival box - standard 85-35)
      - Simon Fraser University Calendar 2004-2005, F-85-5-6-0-40-1
    - 2005-06 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-41; F-85-5-3-0-11 (Archival box - standard 85-35)
      - Simon Fraser University 2005-2006 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-41-1
    - 2006-07 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-42; F-85-5-3-0-11 (Archival box - standard 85-35)
      - Simon Fraser University 2006/2007 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-42-1
    - 2007-08 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-43; F-85-5-3-0-12 (Archival box - standard 85-39)
      - Simon Fraser University Calendar 2007 | 2008, F-85-5-6-0-43-1
    - 2008-09 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-44; F-85-5-3-0-12 (Archival box - standard 85-39)
      - Simon Fraser University Calendar 2008 | 2009
    - 2009-10 Calendar, F-85-5-6-0-45; F-85-5-3-0-12 (Archival box - standard 85-39)
      - Simon Fraser University Calendar 2009 | 2010, F-85-5-6-0-45-1